A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
The Library of Virginia
42401
96.1 cu. ft. (161 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Transferred 2006
Biographical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governor's top management team, or secretariats. The General Assembly in 1972 created six Secretariat positions initially. As government reorganized that number fluctuated as government agencies expanded or consolidated. Currently there are eight secretariats in state government: the Secretary of Administration; Secretary of Commerce and Trade; Secretary of Education; Secretary of Finance; Secretary of Health and Human Resources; Secretary of Natural Resources; Secretary of Public Safety; and the Secretary of Transportation.
The secretariat responsible for human services, health and welfare has gone through several reorganizations. In 1972, the General Assembly passed an act establishing the Secretary of Human Affairs. This office was responsible for management and direction of health and human services provided by the state for the citizens of the commonwealth. In 1976, the secretariat's name changed to the Secretary of Human Resources. With reorganization of state government, the secretariat name changed again to the Secretary of Health and Human Resources in 1988. The secretary has authority over the following agencies or councils: Dept. for the Rights of Virginians with Disabilities; Dept. for the Aging; Dept. of Health; Dept. of Health Professionals; Dept. of Medical Assistance Services; Virginia Health Services Cost Review Council; Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services; Dept. of Rehabilitation Services; Dept. of Social Services; Governors Employment and Training Dept.; Dept. for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing; Virginia Council on Child Care; and Early Childhood Programs. The Secretary also serves on several advisory councils, committees, boards and interstate compacts.
This accession documents the term of Jane H. Woods as the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources from 2002 until 2006, as part of the Mark R. Warner administration.
Scope and Content
The collection is arranged into nine series: I: Briefing Books; II. Constituent Correspondence; III. Correspondence; IV. Correspondence with State Agencies; V. Legislative Files; VI. Legislative Studies; VII. Special Assistant Files; VIII. Special Projects; and IX. Media. The series are loosely based on the original arrangement when transferred.
Series I: Briefing Books, 2002-2006 [bulk 2002-2005], contains the calendar of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources and includes individual calendar pages, notes regarding appointments, invitations to events, and other related materials. The materials within this series are arranged chronologically, and foldered by week.
Series II: Constituent Correspondence, 2000-2006 [bulk 2002-2005], contains correspondence received from constituents, with many being assigned a tracking number for use in the correspondence tracking system used by the governor's office. Items are arranged by tracking number, when available, and date when a tracking number is not present. These materials in particular contain privacy-protected information, and those materials are subject to review prior to viewing. Topics of correspondence range from experiences in working with state agencies under the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, health-related issues, and the general public welfare. Items within this series include correspondence, notes, email, and supporting documentation sent by constituents as it relates to the topic at hand.
Series III: Correspondence, 1997-2006 [bulk 2001-2005], contains general correspondence addressed to the Secretary of Health and Human Resources. Topics addressed are similar to those in Series II: Constituent Correspondence and include discussions of health- and public welfare-related concerns, and include correspondence from a broader range of individuals, including the general public, and state, local, and federal government officials. Items within this series include correspondence, email, notes, and supporting documentation as submitted by correspondents.
Series IV: Correspondence with State Agencies, 1997-2005 [bulk 2002-2005], contains correspondence, notes, email, publications, and other items related to the interaction between the office of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources and the agencies that fall under that office. Items within this series are arranged alphabetically by agency name, and then alphabetically by folder title. Topics covered are often related to budget, decision memos, policy issues, and programs administered by the individual state agencies concerned.
Series V: Legislative Files, 2002-2005, contains correspondence, notes, and copies of legislation related to the state agencies under the Secretary of Health and Human Resources. Items are arranged by Virginia Administrative Code number or Legislative Session number, as appropriate.
Series VI: Legislative Studies, 1999-2004 [bulk 2002-2003], contains correspondence, notes and other materials created to support legislative issues and concerns of the state agencies under the Secretary of Health and Human Resources. Items are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Series VII: Special Assistant Files, 2002-2005, contain correspondence, notes, meeting notes, and other materials on general topics of concern within the office of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources. Items are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Series VIII: Special Projects, 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005], contain correspondence, notes, and other materials related to legislation, topics of concern within the office of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources. Items are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Series IX: Media, 2002-2005, contains cds, videotapes, and computer diskettes found within the entire collection, some of which are oversized. Arranged alphabetically by title.
Some topics of note within the collection include public health, state and federal public assistance programs, the use of biosolids for agricultural purposes, rural plumbing and septic systems, the temporary housing of individuals diplaced by Hurricane Katrina in 2005, regulation of assisted living facilities, and the management of state-operated health facilities.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into nine series: I: Briefing Books; II. Constituent Correspondence; III. Correspondence; IV. Correspondence with State Agencies; V. Legislative Files; VI. Legislative Studies; VII. Special Assistant Files; VIII. Special Projects; and IX. Media. The series are loosely based on the original arrangement when transferred.
Contents List
- Series I: Briefing Books, 2002-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
  - 2002 Jan-21-Jan 27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2002 Jan 28 - Feb 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2002 Feb 4 - 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2002 Feb 11 - 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2002 Feb 18-22 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2002 Feb 25 - 3 Mar (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2002 Mar 4-10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2002 Mar 11-17 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2002 Mar 18-24 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 2002 Mar 25-31 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2002 Apr 1-7 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 2002 Apr 15-21 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 2002 Apr 22-28 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2002 Apr 29 - May 5 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2002 May 6-12 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 2002 May 13-19 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 2002 May 20-26 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 2002 May 27 - June 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 2002 June 2-9 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 2002 June 10-16 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 2002 June 17-23 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 2002 June 24-30 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 2002 July 1-7 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 2002 July 8-14 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 2002 July 15-21 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 2002 July 22-28 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 2002 July 29 - Aug 4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 2002 Aug 5-11 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 2002 Aug 12-18 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 2002 Aug 19-25 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 2002 Aug 26 - Sept 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 2002 Sept 2-8 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 2002 Sept 9-15 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 2002 Sept 16-22 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 2002 Sept 23-29 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 2002 Sept 30-Oct 6 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 2002 Oct 7-13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 2002 Oct 14-20 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 2002 Oct 21-27 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 2002 Oct 28 - Nov 3 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 2002 Nov 4-10 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 2002 Nov 11-17 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 2002 Nov 18-24 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 2002 Nov 25 - Dec 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 2002 Dec 2-8 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 2002 Dec 9-15 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 2002 Dec 16-22 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 2002 Dec 23-31 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 2002 Dec 30 - 2003 Jan 5 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Jan 6-12 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 2003 Jan 13-19 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 2003 Jan 20-26 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 2003 Jan 27 - Feb 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 2003 Feb 3-9 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 2003 Feb 10-16 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 2003 Feb 17-23 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 2003 Feb 24 - Mar 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Mar 3-9 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 2003 Mar 10-16 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 2003 Mar 17-23 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 2003 Mar 24-30 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 2003 Mar 31 - Apr 6 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 2003 Apr 7-13 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 2003 Apr 14-20 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 2003 Apr 21-27 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 2003 Apr 28 - May 4 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 2003 May 5-11 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 2003 May 12-18 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 2003 May 19-25 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 2003 May 26 - June 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 2003 June 2-8 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 2003 June 9-15 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 2003 June 16-22 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 2003 June 23-29 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 2003 June 30 - July 6 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 2003 July 7-13 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 2003 July 14-20 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 2003 July 21-27 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 2003 July 28 - Aug 3 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 2003 Aug 4-10 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 2003 Aug 11-17 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 2003 Aug 18-24 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 2003 Aug 25-31 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 2003 Sept 1-7 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 2003 Sept 8-14 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 2003 Sept 15-21 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 2003 Sept 22-28 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Sept 29 - Oct 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2003 Oct 6-12 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 2003 Oct 13-19 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 2003 Oct 20-26 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 2003 Oct 27 - Nov 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 2003 Nov 3-9 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 2003 Nov 10-16 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Nov 17-23 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 2003 Nov 24-30 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 2003 Dec 1-7 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 2003 Dec 8-14 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 2003 Dec 15-21 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 2003 Dec 22-28 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Dec 29 - 2004 Jan 4 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 2004 Jan 5-11 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 2004 Jan 12-18 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 2004 Jan 19-25 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 2004 Jan 25 - Feb 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 2004 Feb 2-8 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 2004 Feb 9-15 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 2004 Feb 16-22 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 2004 Feb 23-29 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 2004 Mar 1-7 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 2004 Mar 8-14 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 2004 Mar 15-21 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 2004 Mar 22-28 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 2004 Mar 29 - Apr 4 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 2004 Apr 5-11 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 2004 Apr 12-18 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 2004 Apr 19-25 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 2004 Apr 26 - May 2 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 2004 May 3-9 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 2004 May 10-16 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 2004 May 24-31 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 2004 June 1-6 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 2004 June 7-13 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 2004 June 14-20 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 2004 June 21-27 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 2004 June 28 - July 4 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 2004 July 5-11 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 2004 July 12-18 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 2004 July 19-25 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 2004 July 26 - Aug 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 2004 Aug 2-8 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 2004 Aug 9-15 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 2004 Aug 16-22 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 2004 Aug 23-29 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 2004 Aug 30 - Sept 5 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 2004 Sept 6-12 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 2004 Sept 13-19 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - 2004 Sept 20-26 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 2004 Sept 27- Oct 3 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - 2004 Oct 4-10 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 2004 Oct 11-17 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 2004 Oct 18-24 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 2004 Oct 25-31 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 2004 Nov 1-7 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 2004 Nov 8-14 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 2004 Nov 15-21 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 2004 Nov 22-28 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 2004 Nov 29 - Dec 5 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 2004 Dec 6-12 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 2004 Dec 13-19 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 2004 Dec 20-26 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 2004 Dec 27 - 2005 Jan 2 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 2005 Jan 3-9 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 2005 Jan 10-16 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 2005 Jan 17-23 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 2005 Jan 24-30 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - 2005 Jan 31 - Feb 6 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 2005 Feb 7-13 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 2005 Feb 14-20 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - 2005 Feb 21-27 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 2005 Feb 28 - Mar 6 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - 2005 Mar 7-13 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - 2005 Mar 14-20 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - 2005 Mar 21-27 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - 2005 Mar 28 - Apr 3 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 2005 Apr 4-10 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 2005 Apr 11-17 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 2005 Apr 18-24 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 2005 Apr 25 - May 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 2005 May 2-8 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2005 May 9-15 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 2005 May 16-22 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 2005 May 23-29 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 2005 May 30 - June 5 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 2005 June 6-12 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 2005 June 13-19 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 2005 June 20-26 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 2005 June 27 - July 3 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 2005 July 4-10 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 2005 July 11-17 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 2005 July 18-24 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 2005 July 25-31 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - 2005 Aug 1-7 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - 2005 Aug 8-14 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 2005 Aug 15-21 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - 2005 Aug 22-28 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - 2005 Aug 29 - Sept 4 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - 2005 Sept 5-11 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - 2005 Sept 12-18 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - 2005 Sept 19-25 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - 2005 Sept 26 - Oct 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 2005 Oct 3-9 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 2005 Oct 10-16 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 2005 Oct 17-23 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 2005 Oct 24-30 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 2005 Oct 31 - Nov 6 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 2005 Nov 7-13 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 2005 Nov 14-20 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 2005 Nov 21-27 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 2005 Nov 28 - Dec 4 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 2005 Dec 5-11 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 2005 Dec 12-18 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 2005 Dec 19 - 2006 Jan 1 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 2006 Jan 2-9 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Series II: Constituent Correspondence, 2000-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2000125-2000493 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2000637-3001292 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2001325-2002600 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2002617-2003097 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2003125-2004265 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2004269-2004711 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2003730-2005101 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2005102-2005168 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2005167-2005646 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2005644-2006415 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2006149-2006670 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2007687-2007996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 2010848 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2008005-2008261 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2008262-2008585 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2008853-2010213 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2010228-2010688 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2010848 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 202850-2011929 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2011910-2016708 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2016720-2017412 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2018506-2020615 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2020894-2023855 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2024076-2031170 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2031343-2032933 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2033051-2035019 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2011930-2015363 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2013065-2013876 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2013973-2045025 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2015033-2015295 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2015296-2045479 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2015481-2015657 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2035282-2038135 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2038176-2038626 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2037643-2039959 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2040565-2040918 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2049093-2053187 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2053775-2058351 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2058384-2065764 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2065793-2068360 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2068376-2071462 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2071467-2074812 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2074868-2076826 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2076936-2076913 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2081152-2085452 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2085514-2093960 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2094199-2110922 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2111468-2155818 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2156229-2172374 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 217924-2201975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2202479-2212464 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2212592-2226967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2227407-2246501 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2246521-2258209 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2058210-2283322 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2283546-2311024 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2311478-2339530 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2339562-2356218 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2356604-2368305 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2368351-2388853 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2388789-2049627 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2409897-2425761 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2425762-242953 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2429721-2433005 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2423089-2438484 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2438495 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2438692-2447613 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2447934-2462410 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2462743-2468729 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2469929-2475513 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2475709-2482859 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2483085-2487217 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2487238-2489417 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2489499-2497117 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2497160-2509147 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Correspondence, A (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, B (folder 1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, B (folder 2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, C (folder 1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, C (folder 2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, D (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, E (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, F (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, G (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, H (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, I (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, J (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, K (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Correspondence, L (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Correspondence, M (folder 1 of 3) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Constituent Correspondence, M (folder 2 of 3) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Constituent Correspondence, M (folder 3 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, N (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, O (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, P (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, R (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, S (folder 1 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, S (folder 2 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Correspondence, S (folder 3 of 3) (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Correspondence, T (folder 1 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Correspondence, T (folder 2 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, U (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, V (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, W (folder 1 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, W (folder 2 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Z (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Loose materials, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Constituent Correspondence (Oversize): Map of 1600 Block Town Picket, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2000114-2000155, 2002 Jan - Mar (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence, 2000157-2000520, 2002 Jan - Mar (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence, 2010072-2011442 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence, 2011471-2026405 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2026407-2031976 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence, 2032102-2037992 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2038021-2041986 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence 2042020-2049281 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2050816-2058919 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2059144-2063953 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2064127-2068963 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2069050-2071907 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2071960-2075785 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2077009-2081892 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2082762-2086044 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2086048-2086883 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2086893-2087687 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2087773-2088827 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence, 2000 Aug - Oct (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2000 Oct - 2001 Feb (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2001 Feb-Apr (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2001 Apr - Aug (Box 78, Folder 4)